Evil rises from the depths of hell.
Faust: Love of the Damned is a horror, fantasy,
action film directed by Brian Yuzna.
An artist sells his soul to the mysterious M in order to get
revenge on the people who killed his girlfriend.
Soon, he realises everything has a price, and he is transformed
into a horned demon with a passion for killing.
John Jaspers / Faust, played by Mark Frost.
Jade de Camp, played by Isabel Brook.
Blue, played by Jennifer Rope.
Lt. Dan Margolies, played by Jeffrey Combs.
Claire, played by Mònica van Campen.
Newscaster, played by Leslie Charles.
Faust: Love of the Damned (Title in Spain: Faust: La venganza está en la sangre) is a 2000
Spanish English-language superhero horror film directed by Brian Yuzna.
It is adapted from a screenplay by David Quinn and Miguel Tejada-Flores based on
the comic book of the same name by Tim Vigil and David Quinn.
It was produced by Ted Chalmers, Carlos Fernández Rodríguez, Julio Fernández Rodríguez
and Antonio Fernández, Bea Morillas, Miguel Torrente and Brian Yuzna.
The film, which was the first of nine to be produced by Filmax's Fantastic Factory label, won the award
for Best Special Effects at the 2000 Catalan International Film Festival in Sitges, Spain.
The film explores themes of rape, snake, magic, gangster, cemetery.
The tone is dark.